[
    {
        "question": "Who is responsible for all estimates in the Product Backlog?",
        "option1": "The Scrum Master",
        "option2": "The Product Owner",
        "option3": "The Scrum Team",
        "option4": "The Development Team",
        "option5": "The Product Owner and the Scrum Master",
        "answer": 4
    },

    {
        "question": "Who is responsible for the Product Backlog?",
        "option1": "The Product Owner and the Scrum Master",
        "option2": "The Scrum Master and The Development Team",
        "option3": "The Scrum Team",
        "option4": "The Development Team",
        "option5": "The Product Owner",
        "answer": 5
    },

    {
        "question": "The timebox for the Sprint Review is:",
        "option1": "4 hours for a monthly Sprint. For shorter Sprints it is usually shorter.",
        "option2": "1 day",
        "option3": "As long as needed",
        "option4": "2 hours",
        "option5": "4 hours and longer as needed",
        "answer": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "Who is allowed to participate in the Daily Scrum?",
        "option1": "The Key Stakeholders",
        "option2": "The Scrum Master",
        "option3": "The Development Team",
        "option4": "The Product Owner",
        "option5": "The Team Manager",
        "answer": 3
    },

    {
        "question": "When does the next Sprint begin?",
        "option1": "Next Monday",
        "option2": "Immediately after the conclusion of the previous Sprint",
        "option3": "Immediately following the next Sprint Planning",
        "option4": "When the Product Owner is ready",
        "option5": "Next Month",
        "answer": 2
    },

    {
        "question": "When is a Sprint over?",
        "option1": "When the timebox expires",
        "option2": "Immediately after the conclusion of the previous Sprint",
        "option3": "When all the tasks are completed",
        "option4": "When the Product Owner says it is done",
        "option5": "When the Scrum Master says it is done",
        "answer": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "Which Scrum events are timeboxed?",
        "option1": "Release Retrospective",
        "option2": "Sprint Testing",
        "option3": "Refinement",
        "option4": "Sprint Retrospective",
        "option5": "Sprint Testing",
        "answer": 4
    },

    {
        "question": "What is the recommended size for a Scrum Team?",
        "option1": "7 plus or minus 2",
        "option2": "9",
        "option3": "Typically 10 or fewer people",
        "option4": "15 or more",
        "option5": "Minimum of 8",
        "answer": 3
    },

    {
        "question": "What does it mean to say that an event has a timebox?",
        "option1": "The event must take at least a minimum amount of time",
        "option2": "The event must happen at a set time",
        "option3": "The event has no time expiration",
        "option4": "The event must happen by a given time",
        "option5": "The event can take no more than a maximum amount of time",
        "answer": 5
    },

    {
        "question": "During a Sprint, a Developer determines that the Scrum Team will not be able to complete the items in their forecast. Who should be present to review and adjust the Product Backlog items selected?",
        "option1": "The Scrum Master, the project manager, and the Developers",
        "option2": "The Product Owner and the Developers",
        "option3": "The Scrum Master",
        "option4": "The Product Owner and all stakeholders",
        "option5": "The Developers",
        "answer": 2
    },

    {
        "question": "What is the main reason for the Scrum Master to be at the Daily Scrum?",
        "option1": "They do not have to be there; they only need to ensure the Developers have a Daily Scrum",
        "option2": "To gather status and progress information to report to management",
        "option3": "To write down any changes to the Sprint Backlog, including adding new items, and tracking progress on the burn-down",
        "option4": "To make sure every team member answers the three questions",
        "option5": "To make sure that the team members do not expire 15 minutes",
        "answer": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "The length of a Sprint should be:",
        "option1": "Short enough to keep the business risk acceptable to the Product Owner",
        "option2": "Short enough to be able to synchronize the development work with other business events",
        "option3": "2 months",
        "option4": "One month or less",
        "option5": "Questions A, B and D are correct",
        "answer": 5
    },

    {
        "question": "Who creates the Definition of Done?",
        "option1": "The Manager",
        "option2": "The Product Owner since they are responsible for the product's success",
        "option3": "If it is not an organizational standard, the Scrum Team must create a Definition of Done appropriate for the product",
        "option4": "The Scrum Master since they are responsible for the productivity of the Developers",
        "option5": "The Scrum Team, in a collaborative effort where the result is the common denominator of all members' definitions",
        "answer": 3
    },

    {
        "question": "What is the role of Management in Scrum?",
        "option1": "Support the Product Owner with insights and information into high value product and system capabilities. Support the Scrum Master to cause organizational change that fosters empiricism, self-management, bottom-up intelligence, and intelligent product delivery",
        "option2": "Identify and remove people that are not working hard enough",
        "option3": "Continually monitor staffing levels of the Scrum Team",
        "option4": "Monitor the progress of the Developers on the Scrum Team",
        "option5": "Monitor all the team to check if the work is going well",
        "answer": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "Who should know the most about the progress toward a business objective or a release, and be able to explain the alternatives most clearly?",
        "option1": "The Project Manager",
        "option2": "The Scrum Master",
        "option3": "The Developers",
        "option4": "The Team Leader",
        "option5": "The Product Owner",
        "answer": 5
    }

]

